welcome to this quick video of using
欢迎观看此使用视频
flow with batch jobs in spring XD so the
在Spring XD中与批处理作业一起流动，因此
old version of flow worked for visually
流的旧版本在视觉上起作用
composing your streams this new version
组成您的流此新版本
you can run in xt-1 3 it's for visually
您可以在xt-1 3中运行
composing your chops so orchestrating
精心编排
your jobs so got an XD 1 3 running here
您的工作，所以在这里运行了XD 1 3
most of the standard modules are
大多数标准模块是
registered with a couple of extra ones
注册了几个额外的
these be simple be simple to the both
这些都很简单
variants of the batch simple example you
批处理简单示例的变体
can get off github it does nothing but
可以下车github，但什么也没做
what I'm here is I'm showing you
我在这里是在向你展示
orchestration not how complicate you can
编排不是那么复杂
make a batch job so that's simple we'll
做一个批处理工作，这很简单，我们将
just complete normally straightaway very
刚完成通常很简单
simple to well actually a exit via
很容易实际上通过退出
failed status so that we can see what
失败状态，以便我们可以看到
happens when jobs fail in an
当工作失败时发生
orchestration based on those very simple
基于那些非常简单的业务流程
modules I created some rudimentary
我创建了一些基本模块
definition so we got low database we got
定义，所以我们数据库很低
the create report which might take that
创建报告可能需要
database date and turn into a report the
数据库日期并转换成报告
email report sends it around at a tidy
电子邮件报告整齐发送
up job so these are meant to be slightly
工作，所以这些应该是稍微
more representative of the real world
更具现实意义
but obviously they're based on these
但显然他们是基于这些
modules that don't actually do anything
实际上什么都不做的模块
under the covers and we're going to use
在幕后，我们将使用
these to compose a job so the UI looks a
这些组成工作，因此用户界面看起来像
little similar to what we have the
有点类似于我们所拥有的
streams only the users got a bit more
流仅用户获得更多
power this time depth palette is filled
这次填充深度调色板电源
with some control nodes I'm not going to
与一些控制节点，我不会
cover those in this video that's for
涵盖本视频中的
future more advanced video but you'll
未来更高级的视频，但您会
see definitions is everything I just
看到定义就是我的一切
showed you on the definitions page ready
在定义页面上向您展示了
to use in the job you're going to build
在您要建立的工作中使用
so every job has to start in an end and
所以每项工作都必须从头开始，
you get these red markers if there's any
如果有任何标记，您会得到这些红色标记
problems with your job so it says
你的工作有问题，所以说
nothing nothing's leading to end State
没有什么没有导致最终状态
so there's no no real job here so let's
所以这里没有真正的工作，所以让我们
create something so I am going to drag
创建一些东西，所以我要拖
out load a base and I'm gonna drag it
卸下底座，我将其拖曳
out
出
create report put a simple job no you
创建报告就可以完成简单的工作
see I created it by dragging out the
看到我通过拖出
modules and then drawing in the links
模块，然后绘制链接
there is a slightly faster way if you
如果您有一个更快的方法
drag out if you already have the links
如果已有链接，则将其拖出
and you say insert modules into that
你说插入模块
flow
流
you can't just drop them on you'll see
你不能只是把它们放在你会看到
that highlights say I'm going to drop
突出显示我要放弃
into this blow with a little crib port
带着一点婴儿床端口进入打击
drop that onto here so see what we've
放到这里，所以看看我们已经
done now is we didn't have to do any
现在要做的是我们不必做任何事情
fill in with links and we built the same
填写链接，我们建立了相同的
thing you open the DSL view you'll see
您打开DSL视图所看到的
the jobs the SLI slightly different
SLI的工作略有不同
those streams in SL this is how you
SL中的这些流，这就是您的方式
express a job flow so the number of
表示工作流程，因此
things to run in a sequence and using
事情要按顺序运行并使用
this double pipe notation to join them
这种双管道符号加入他们
together so let's define that compose
一起定义一下组成
job I hope you jump onto the definitions
工作，我希望你跳入定义
page we'll see it and we can expand
页面，我们将看到它，并且我们可以扩展
compose jobs on here to get a view of
在这里撰写工作，以了解
them picture of them can be helpful when
他们的照片可以帮助您
the DSO gets a bit complicated it should
DSO有点复杂，应该
be ready to go on the deployments page
准备好进入“部署”页面
demo one let's launch it that will make
演示一，让我们启动它将使
it run and then we should see the
它运行，然后我们应该看到
results of that run on the executions
执行结果
page totally completely could remember
页面完全可以记住
those simple things do nothing so we see
这些简单的事情什么也没做，所以我们看到
that it did a load database in the
它在
create report it was great now not all
创建报告这很棒，现在还不是全部
jobs succeed every time so let's do
每次工作都会成功，所以我们做吧
something a bit more elaborate so I'm
一些更详细的东西，所以我
going to start out the same so we're
要开始一样，所以我们
going to load the database we're going
要加载数据库，我们要
to usually create a called X talk that
通常创建一个称为X的谈话
wait a minute and then email
请稍等，然后发送电子邮件
so this is the same as before craveable
所以这跟以前渴望的一样
x is a variant of Korea report that uses
x是韩国报告的变体，使用
that job module is hard-coded to fail so
该作业模块被硬编码为失败，因此
this guy is going to mix it with a
这个家伙要与一个混合
failed exit status and batch terms now
失败的退出状态和批处理条款现在
these solid lines tend to represent what
这些实线往往代表什么
happens in the happy path wing every job
发生在每条工作的快乐之路
completes successfully if your jobs that
如果您的工作成功完成
are going to have different exit
将会有不同的出口
statuses you can actually define
您可以实际定义的状态
alternative glows so here I am adding in
替代发光，所以我在这里添加
a tidy up job but I only wanted to run
整理工作，但我只想跑步
if this job X is why failure only if it
如果这项工作X是为什么只有失败
completes normally I want to read email
正常完成，我想阅读电子邮件
report so when I hover on the link
报告，以便当我将鼠标悬停在链接上时
you'll see I get a cog
你会看到我得到一个齿轮
click on that and it tells me I'm
点击它，它告诉我我
setting the properties for this link
设置此链接的属性
between these two jobs and I can set the
在这两个工作之间，我可以设置
job exits things so now you can see
工作退出的事情，所以现在你可以看到
there that if create report X fails
如果创建报告X失败
we'll run tardy up if it succeeds we'll
如果成功，我们会拖延时间
run email report this jobs well-formed
运行电子邮件报告此作业格式正确
let's that's right to gauge on the
让我们来衡量一下
deployments and she'll be ready to go
部署，她会准备出发
and launch that
然后启动
two executions get up and you'll see
两次处决，你会看到
what happened is yeah hello database
是怎么回事你好数据库
round that succeeded then it's really
回合成功了，那真的
completed great report axe rounding X
完成了很棒的报告斧四舍五入
advisor failing that course is to take
不能通过该课程的顾问
that transitional link to the tidy up
到整齐的过渡环节
job which then completely ignore me
然后完全忽略我的工作
so there's no sign of the email report
因此没有电子邮件报告的迹象
running okay so that's how you can do
运行正常，这就是您可以做的
simple flows and then introduced
简单流程然后介绍
conditional flows depending on the job
有条件的流动取决于工作
exit status that comes out of a job
工作退出状态
now you can run things in parallel doing
现在您可以并行运行
the split in batch terms so suppose I
分批拆分，所以假设我
have multiple jobs in fact that can load
实际上有多个可以加载的作业
up a database in three days up one of
在三天内建立一个数据库
these links being made conditioner this
这些链接被调节
is saying I wanna run these three things
是说我想跑这三件事
at the same time okay so this says
同时好吧，这说
create reports only gonna run once these
创建报告只能运行一次
three guys have been done look at the
三个家伙已经看完了
DSL how's that expressed this is how you
DSL表示这是您的方式
express my split so the angle brackets
表达我的分裂，所以尖括号
demarcated the beginning and end and
划定起点和终点，
then the ampersand indicate what you
然后“＆”号指示您
want to run in parallel so here we got
想并行运行，所以我们在这里
low database to run in parallel with low
低数据库与低并行运行
database - and parallel with low
数据库-与低并行
database things and there's nothing to
数据库的东西，没有什么可做的
stop you mixing up these splits and
停止您混合这些拆分并
close so suppose I let's just grab a
关闭，假设我让我们抓住
random job so now I've said that these
随机工作，所以现在我说这些
single jobs are running in parallel with
单个作业与
these two jobs that are going to main
这两个主要工作
sequence and I'm showing you this effort
顺序，我正在向您展示这一努力
to create a nicer grass you can break up
创造更好的草可以分解
these links just click in the middle of
这些链接只需点击中间的
them
他们
a point you can do it's up some nice
你可以做到的一点很好
craftsman take some screenshots didn't
工匠拍了一些截图没
need orientation so he able to do
需要定向，所以他能够做
something like that you can see it just
这样的东西，你可以看到它
mixed the concept so no database in
混合了概念，所以没有数据库
payment parallel was low database to in
付款并行是数据库不足
parallel with this flow on these two
与这两个流程平行
things now you can mix these things up
现在，您可以将这些东西混合在一起
with the transitional things as well so
过渡的东西也是如此
low database hex you exit with a failure
数据库低十六进制错误退出
so we can create a additional link here
因此我们可以在此处创建其他链接
so if they database execute it's
所以如果他们执行数据库
normally or run demo to if otherwise
正常运行，否则运行演示
we're gonna tidy up and then will run
我们要整理一下然后运行
create report because these guys may
创建报告，因为这些人可能
have put some useful in database anyway
无论如何已经在数据库中添加了一些有用的东西
so that's how you build basic flows and
这就是建立基本流程的方式
splits using flow and how you use
使用流程和使用方式进行拆分
transitional links there is more stuff
过渡链接还有更多的东西
you can do including why you need these
您可以包括为什么需要这些
control notes but that's for a future
控制笔记，但这是为了未来
video thank you for watching
视频感谢您的观看